Mazen Mohamed Ibrahim Junior Front End Developer

≥ mazenfadl32@gmail.com

01155212867

• Cairo-Egypt

https://github.com/zero-Mazen

in www.linkedin.com/in/mazen-fadl-595aa81a5

Military Service : completed

I am a highly qualified information systems specialist with the ability to design websites, networks, and database management. I have strong technical skills as well as excellent interpersonal skills, which allow me to interact with a wide range of clients. I am excited to take on the challenge to grow and improve my IT skills. I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, and hard-working person.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer(Training), Fawaterk

Practical training in the field of front-end development in Six months

10/2022 - 03/2023 6th of October City, Egypt

Technical Support, TE-Data

A Technical Support Engineer provides customer service for computer hardware and software. They troubleshoot issues related to their company's accounts or any other miscellaneous tasks in the field as determined by their manager

08/2021 – 10/2022 Nasr City, Egypt

EDUCATION

Bachelor degree of Information System(VeryGood),

Faculty of Computer and informatics, Zagazig University

06/2015 - 07/2019 sharqia, Egypt

គ្ល^ង MY PROJECTS

https://github.com/zero-Mazen/My-portifolio-portfolio1, --- MY Portfolio

A web I designed it to show a brief profile of myself and the projects that I do

https://github.com/zero-Mazen/CRUD-Project, (https://zero-mazen.github.io/CRUD-Project/)----CRUD Project a project that enters the name, price, type of product, and description of the product, which the customer enters and displays in a table

https://github.com/zero-Mazen/project1, (https://zero-mazen.github.io/project1/)---lion project is a project made by HTML & CSS

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- BootStrap
- SASS

• JS

- TypeScript
- JQuery

- Git/Github
- Angular

S LANGUAGES

Arabic (Native) • English (Good)